Then we are back with ten unnecessary
Facts that you may not know about.
I was going to start directly with a small question.
What do you think first came the postit note or calculator?
Do you think a bundle of paper with a faint glue
As you can make small notes on Come first?
Or do you think an electronic calculator who can math
came first?
It was actually the calculator.
Believe it or not.
What would a snail with human teeth look like?
Okay, we're moving on.
The smell of the moon.
Astronauts who visited the moon reported afterwards
that the moon's dust has a very distinct smell,
Similar burnt powder or wet ash.
According to Thai law it is
illegal to harm, destroy or show a lack of respect for banknotes or
Coins containing depictions of the king or other members of the royal family.
This includes actions such as pedaling or tearing down banknotes.
It is a crime to insult, threaten or slander the king, queen, successor or regent.
Giraffes are among the mammals that sleep least.
In the wild, giraffes sleep only about 30 minutes per day.
This short sleeping time is often distributed in short
naps that last for a few minutes at a time.
Because giraffes need to be alert to avoid predators' attacks.
Newborn calves sleep more, but are also protected by other giraffes that watch over them.
Giraffes can sleep both standing and lying down, but adult giraffes
often prefer to sleep standing to be able to quickly escape from predators.
In captivity you might be allowed to sleep longer
up to 6 hours per day on average.
Mercury is the only metallic element that is
The world's first SMS that incidentally stands for short
Message Service was sent on December 3.
1992 by Neil Papworth
A test engineer in the UK.
The message was sent from Neil's computer to a manager at Vodafone,
Richard Jarvis, and obeyed Merry Christmas.
This historic SMS marked the beginning of
a new era in digital communication and although less sms is sent today
Due to all apps used, such as WhatsApp, Snapchat and Messenger and so on,
So it will still be sent about 23 \ hillion
SMS every day around the world.